Just one more treat
is all
my glorious feast
needs to be all complete
Don't you agree?
I'm thinking of a dish
it's real tangy but sweet
however...
baking you two together...
ALL PART OF MY
KEY
KEY LIME
your mangled corpse
is all we really need
to complete the menu
flambe your bodies
no you wont be sorry
just one more slice
and we'll start the party
when will you see...
You're
You're my
You're my treat
And when you rot under the tree
just the perfect gift for me!
Frozen oh so blissfully
Your just like good ol' Natalie<
FA LA LA LA~
this Christmas season
wouldn't feel complete
without this dish
roasting you alive
wouldn't be unwise
but hey, sorry pal!
YOU WONT SURVIVE!
so wont you please
give up yourselves for me
an experiment like you
doesn't have the choice to hide or flee
rip out your EYES
scoop out that SLIME
say you're goodBYES
I will eat you both alive
dear all my friends
seems it's finally time
to start this feast
bring in the trollies
they'll be no follies
as we all feast
on your dismembered bodies
and now you see...
my flawless feast
you resist so adamantly but
your already cooked to me now
crystal garnish
on your carcass
leave guests astonished and
start the carnage
and
and so
and so now
and so now we
and so now we dine...
it's dinner time...
So set the table
and light the candles
and cut me a slice of that
KEY
KEY LIME
KEY LIME PIE